Inventory of the Edwin Meese papers, 1941-1991
Hoover Institution Archives
- Gubernatorial Administration of Ronald Reagan File, 1941-1976 (Boxes 128-554, 772-773, Film shelf)
  - Education
    - Education vocational/career, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 197: 4)
    - Vocational education and technical training, 1971 (Box-folder 197: 5-6)
    - Vocational education and "salable skill" legislation, 1973 (Box-folder 197: 7)
    - Western Interstate Commission on Higher Education, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 197: 8-11)
    - Campus Studies Institute, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 197: 12-13)
    - Education ROTC, military, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 198: 1)
    - Student aid, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 198: 2-3)
    - California Community Colleges, 1973 (Box-folder 198: 4)
    - State Board of Education, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 198: 5-6)
    - State Department of Education, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 198: 7-8)
    - Department of Education, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 198: 9)
    - Proposed reorganization of the California State Department of Education, undated (Box-folder 198: 10)
    - Department of Education, superintendent of public instruction, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 198: 11)
    - Education, finance, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 198: 12-16)
    - Education, finance (cont'd.), 1969-1974 (Box-folder 199: 1-6)
    - Public school finances, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 199: 7-8)
    - School finance, 1969 (Box-folder 199: 9)
    - School finance legislation, 1972 (Box-folder 199: 10)
    - Proposed task force on impact of Serrano decision, 1972 (Box-folder 199: 11)
    - Questions and answers on school finance, 1971 (Box-folder 199: 12)
    - Higher education finance, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 199: 13-16)
    - Education Reform Commission, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 200: 1-3)
    - Education Task Force, 1970 (Box-folder 200: 4)
    - Federal funds for academic science, fiscal year, 1970 (Box-folder 200: 5)
    - Guidelines for increasing efficiency in graduate education, 1971 (Box-folder 200: 6)
    - Higher cost programs in California public higher education, 1971 (Box-folder 200: 7)
    - Federal support to universities, colleges and selected nonprofit institutions, fiscal year 1971 (Box-folder 200: 8)
    - Legislation, education, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 200: 9-12)
    - Legislation, education (cont'd.), 1968-1974 (Box-folder 201: 1-4)
    - Legislation, education, Abizzer, 1970 (Box-folder 201: 5)
    - Programs, education, 1971 (Box-folder 201: 6)
    - Education proposals, 1972 (Box-folder 201: 7-10)
    - ACS Education Program, 1972 (Box-folder 201: 11)
    - Higher education legislation, including campus disorder control, 1969 (Box-folder 201: 12)
    - Education, performance contracting, vocational education, Peck proposals and information binder, 1971 (Box-folder 201: 13)
    - Higher education student aid legislation, 1972 (Box-folder 201: 14)
    - Higher education tuition, 1972 (Box-folder 201: 15)
  - Governor's Office, executive secretary section, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 202: 1-7)
  - Executive unit, 1971 (Box-folder 202: 8)
  - View graph slides, Governor's Office organization, 1969 (Box-folder 202: 9)
  - Memoranda
    - 1971-1973 (Box-folder 202: 10)
    - Mike Deaver/Mike Woodson, 1973 (Box-folder 202: 11)
    - Edwin Meese, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 202: 12-13)
  - Governor's Office, transition, 1974 (Box-folder 202: 14)
  - Memoranda binder, state administration working papers, 1969 (Box-folder 202: 15)
  - History and Archives Project, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 203: 1)
  - Briefings for Ed Meese on return from Europe, 1969 (Box-folder 203: 2)
  - Management review of the state teachers' retirement system, 1974 (Box-folder 203: 3)
  - State teacher retirement, 1974 (Box-folder 203: 4)
  - State Personnel Board, 1974 (Box-folder 203: 5-7)
  - Memoranda, 1974 (Box-folder 203: 8)
  - Memoranda and California State Personnel Board, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 203: 9-10)
  - Compendium of information for transition briefing, 1974 (Box-folder 203: 11)
  - Department of Food and Agriculture, undated (Box-folder 204: 1)
  - Bureau of Animal Health, 1974 (Box-folder 204: 2)
  - Department of Food and Agriculture, 1974 (Box-folder 204: 3-5)
  - Agriculture and Services Agency, 1974 (Box-folder 204: 6)
  - Department of Consumer Affairs, transition report, 1975 (Box-folder 204: 7-11)
  - Department of General Services, binder, 1974 (Box-folder 205: 1-5)
  - Business and Transportation Agency, 1974 (Box-folder 205: 6)
  - Agriculture and Services Agency manual, 1974 (Box-folder 205: 7)
  - Governor's Office, Office of Intergovernmental Management (OIM), 1969-1974 (Box-folder 206: 1-4)
  - Quarterly statewide federal grant activity report, 1972 (Box-folder 206: 5-6)
  - Quarterly grant report, 1972 (Box-folder 206: 7-8)
  - Governor's Office, Office of Intergovernmental Relations (OIR), 1970-1974 (Box-folder 206: 9-10)
  - Council on Intergovernmental Relations
    - 1968-1974 (Box-folder 206: 11-12)
    - 1968-1974 (cont'd.) (Box-folder 207: 1-6)
    - Frankum-Nestande, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 207: 7)
    - 1970-1972 (Box-folder 207: 8-12)
    - "State Services for Local Government" handbook, circa 1974 (Box-folder 208: 1-3)
  - Federal-state relations
    - Governmental relations, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 208: 4-5)
    - Frankum, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 208: 6-7)
    - Governor's Office, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 208: 8-11)
    - Governor's Office (cont'd.), 1967-1974 (Box-folder 209: 1-13)
    - Ron Frankum, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 210: 1-2)
    - State-federal problems, 1970 June (Box-folder 210: 3-4)
    - Intergovernmental Affairs Fellowship Program, 1974 (Box-folder 210: 5)
    - Areas of concern between federal government and state government, 1972 (Box-folder 210: 6-7)
    - Federal-state relations, 1969 (Box-folder 210: 8)
    - Federal Regional Council IX, 1973 (Box-folder 210: 9)
  - Public information report, 1974 (Box-folder 210: 10-12)
  - Public information report (cont'd.), 1974 (Box-folder 211: 1)
  - Pre-emption, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 211: 2-5)
  - Federal and state intervention in California local government, 1974 (Box-folder 211: 6-7)
  - Pre-emption, 1967 (Box-folder 211: 8-9)
  - Governor's Office, revenue sharing, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 211: 10-12)
  - Governor's Office, revenue sharing (cont'd.), 1969-1974 (Box-folder 212: 1-6)
  - Governor's Office, local government, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 212: 7-13)
  - Governor's Office, local government (cont'd.), 1967-1974 (Box-folder 213: 1-10)
  - Local government, state-local relations, fiscal problems, etc., 1967-1973 (Box-folder 213: 11-12)
  - Local government, state-local relations, fiscal problems, etc. (cont'd.), 1967-1973 (Box-folder 214: 1)
  - Local government, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 214: 2-5)
  - Intergovernmental programs, undated (Box-folder 214: 6)
  - Special districts, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 214: 7)
  - Regional boundaries, agencies, etc., 1970-1972 (Box-folder 214: 8)
  - Bay Area Planning Agency proposal, 1971 (Box-folder 214: 9)
  - Bay Area Regional Agency, 1971 (Box-folder 214: 10)
  - Warnings about Baro A.B. 711 and Metro 1313 from Contra Costa voters, 1969 (Box-folder 214: 11)
  - County Supervisor's Association of California meeting, Sacramento, 1971 January 14 (Box-folder 214: 12)
  - County Supervisor's Association of California, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 214: 13-16)
  - California County Fact Book, 1972 (Box-folder 215: 1-2)
  - Legislation affecting counties, 1972 (Box-folder 215: 3-4)
  - Lake Cunningham feasibility study, 1972 (Box-folder 215: 5)
  - Lake Cunningham, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 215: 6-7)
  - City, Magazine of Urban Life and Environment, 1970 (Box-folder 215: 8)
  - League of California Cities, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 215: 9-10)
  - "Salute to City/County Government,", 1967 (Box-folder 215: 11)
  - "Salute to City/County Government" (cont'd.), 1967 (Box-folder 216: 1)
  - Conferences with county officials, 1972 (Box-folder 216: 2)
  - Joint Committee on the Organization and Financing of Local Government, 1972 (Box-folder 216: 3)
  - Supervisor's forum, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 216: 4)
  - Task Force on Local Government Organization, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 216: 5-11)
  - Public benefits from public choice, 1974 (Box-folder 216: 12)
  - "Local Government Boundaries" report, undated (Box-folder 217: 1)
  - Task Force on Local Governmental working papers, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 217: 2-5)
  - "Understanding Urban Government: Metropolitan Reform Reconsidered,", 1973 (Box-folder 217: 6)
  - Capital punishment, 1966-1972
    - General, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 217: 7-8)
    - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 217: 9)
    - Correspondence (cont'd.), 1966-1967 (Box-folder 218: 1)
    - 1972-1974 (Box-folder 218: 2-5)
    - Federal litigation, Hill et al v. Nelson, etc., 1967-1968 (Box-folder 218: 6-10)
    - Gerald H. Gottlieb, ACLU capital punishment, 1967 (Box-folder 218: 11)
    - U.S. death penalty case, 1972 (Box-folder 219: 1)
    - General, 1971 (Box-folder 219: 2)
    - Death row material, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 219: 3-7)
    - Against, 1967 (Box-folder 219: 8)
  - Crime, 1966-1974
    - 1968-1973 (Box-folder 219: 9)
    - 1967 (Box-folder 219: 10-11)
    - 1967-1974 (Box-folder 220: 1-2)
    - Organized, 1968 (Box-folder 220: 3)
    - 1966-1974 (Box-folder 220: 4-8)
  - Governor's Office, legal affairs, 1966-1974
    - 1967-1974 (Box-folder 220: 9-11)
    - Section, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 220: 12)
    - Unit, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 220: 13-14)
    - 1968-1973 (Box-folder 221: 1)
    - Individual case materials, Ed Meese #80, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 221: 2)
    - 1967-1974 (Box-folder 221: 3-5)
  - Extradition and Clemency Secretary, 1965-1967
    - Current work, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 221: 6)
    - Reference material, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 221: 7)
    - Plans and procedure, 1967 (Box-folder 221: 8)
    - California law review comment on clemency, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 221: 9)
    - Clemency hearings, Paul LaVergne, 1967 (Box-folder 221: 10)
    - Clemency actions of past administration, 1966 (Box-folder 221: 11)
    - "Executive Clemency," Ed Meese article, 1969 (Box-folder 221: 12)
    - Acts of executive clemency of California, 1968 (Box-folder 221: 13)
    - Governor's designation of authority to extradition secretary and executive secretary to affix his name to N.P.T. agent's appointments, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 221: 14)
  - Speech material, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 221: 15-16)
  - Speech material, Reagan administration information, 1967 (Box-folder 221: 17)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 221: 18)
  - Legal Affairs Office procedures, 1960-1966 (Box-folder 221: 19-20)
  - Crime control and law enforcement programs, 1968 (Box-folder 221: 21)
  - Governor's Office: Legal Affairs, individual case materials, Ed Meese #80, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 222: 1)
  - Governor Reagan, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 222: 2)
  - Federal crime legislation, 1968 (Box-folder 222: 3)
  - District attorney, 1967 (Box-folder 222: 4)
  - Exclusionary rule, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 222: 5)
  - Office of the Governor, State of California Legal Affairs Unit, 1972 (Box-folder 222: 6)
  - Survey of knowledge of criminal penalties, 1968 (Box-folder 222: 7)
  - Crime and penalties in California, 1968 (Box-folder 222: 8)
  - Cleaver, Black Panther, 1968 (Box-folder 222: 9)
  - Black Panthers, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 222: 10-13)
  - Huey Newton, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 222: 14)
  - Black Panthers, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 223: 1-2)
  - Courts, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 223: 3-11)
  - Legal and judicial system, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 223: 12)
  - Legal and judicial system, problem court decisions, 1972 (Box-folder 223: 13)
  - Preliminary report on the California Lower Court Study, 1971 (Box-folder 223: 14)
  - Judicial Council of California, 1974 (Box-folder 223: 15)
  - Savio appeal to U.S. Supreme Court, Miranda ruling, civil rights case, 1967 (Box-folder 224: 1)
  - Conference of judges, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 224: 2)
  - Appellate courts, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 224: 3)
  - Revision of the federal court appellate system, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 224: 4-6)
  - Task Force on Appellate Court Workload, 1973 (Box-folder 224: 7)
  - Statewide courtroom security, 1970 (Box-folder 224: 8)
  - Judicial reform, 1971-1972
    - General, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 224: 9)
    - Blue Ribbon Committee report, 1972 (Box-folder 224: 10)
    - Report of the Special Judicial Reform Committee, 1971 February (Box-folder 224: 11)
  - Judicial selection, 1941-1973
    - Plan, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 224: 12-14)
    - 1967-1968 (Box-folder 225: 1-3)
    - Retirement system, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 225: 4)
    - Retirement plan, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 225: 5)
    - 1941-1967 (Box-folder 225: 6-9)
    - Plan, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 226: 1-5)
    - Plan legislation, 1969 (Box-folder 226: 6)
    - Plan correspondence and inner-office memoranda, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 226: 7-8)
    - Plan, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 226: 9-10)
  - Task Force on Criminal Justice Legislation, 1969 (Box-folder 226: 11)
  - Governor's Select Committee on Law Enforcement Problems, 1972 (Box-folder 226: 12)
  - Public Safety Task Force, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 226: 13)
  - Select Committee on Law Enforcement, 1972 (Box-folder 227: 1)
  - Task Force, public safety/law enforcement, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 227: 2-5)
  - Controlling crime in California, 1973 (Box-folder 227: 6-7)
  - Task Force to Study Violence, 1974 (Box-folder 227: 8)
  - Firearms control, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 227: 9-11)
  - Pornography/obscenity, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 227: 12-13)
  - "Hollywood Blue" movie, 1971 (Box-folder 228: 1)
  - Proposition 18, obscenity, 1972 (Box-folder 228: 2)
  - Legal affairs, 1968-1974
    - Law enforcement, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 228: 3-9)
    - Bar associations, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 228: 10)
    - Citizens for Law and Order, Citizens for Law Enforcement Needs, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 228: 11)
    - Law enforcement associations, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 228: 12)
    - Law enforcement associations (cont'd.), 1968-1974 (Box-folder 229: 1)
    - Peace officers associations, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 229: 2-4)
    - Peace Officers Research Association of California, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 229: 5)
    - Aid to victims, 1972 (Box-folder 229: 6)
    - Assault on law enforcement personnel, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 229: 7)
    - Rewards for apprehension and conviction, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 229: 8)
    - Legislative changes affecting law enforcement, 1970 (Box-folder 229: 9)
    - Ronald Reagan on law enforcement, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 229: 10)
    - Crime fighting techniques, wiretapping, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 229: 11-12)
    - Los Angeles Emergency Communications System, 1971 (Box-folder 229: 13)
    - Crime on campuses, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 229: 14)
  - Law enforcement/criminal justice, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 229: 15)
  - Law and order, 1968 (Box-folder 230: 1)
  - Public safety, 1973 (Box-folder 230: 2)
  - Juveniles, Junior Deputy Program, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 230: 3)
  - Police-news media relations, 1969 (Box-folder 230: 4)
  - Prevention and control of crime and delinquency, 1965 (Box-folder 230: 5)
  - Legislative changes affecting law enforcement, 1971 (Box-folder 230: 6)
  - Crimes and arrests, 1971 (Box-folder 230: 7)
  - Law enforcement: Berkeley police reorganization proposal, 1971 (Box-folder 230: 8)
  - Demonstrations, riots, and disorders, 1967-1975 (Box-folder 230: 9-11)
  - Law enforcement plans, undated (Box-folder 230: 12)
  - Demonstrations, riots, and disorders, 1966-1975 (Box-folder 231: 1-12)
  - Demonstrations, riots, and disorders (cont'd.), 1966-1975 (Box-folder 232: 1-11)
  - Newspapers, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 233: 1-7)
  - Emergency planning and operations: operations plans, closing of campuses, 1970 (Box-folder 233: 8)
  - McClellan hearing, 1969 (Box-folder 233: 9-10)
  - Students for a Democratic Society (SDS) national convention material, 1969 (Box-folder 233: 11)
  - Students for a Democratic Society (SDS) national convention material (cont'd.), 1969 (Box-folder 234: 1)
  - Riots, civil and criminal disorders, 1970 (Box-folder 234: 2)
  - Campus disorders and law enforcement problems, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 234: 3)
  - Riot prevention program, 1967 (Box-folder 234: 4)
  - Demonstrations in Washington, D.C. in 1971, action, 1972 March 29 (Box-folder 234: 5)
  - Demonstrations, riots, disorders, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 234: 6-10)
  - Speeches, rallies, and demonstrations in public buildings and parks, 1968 (Box-folder 234: 11)
  - National advisory on civil disorders, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 234: 12-13)
  - Commission on civil disorders and campus unrest, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 235: 1)
  - National Advisory Commission on Civil Disorders, 1968 (Box-folder 235: 2)
  - President's Commission on Campus Unrest, 1970 (Box-folder 235: 3-4)
  - Report of the Select Committee on Campus Disturbances, 1969 (Box-folder 235: 5)
  - "Shut It Down! A College in Crisis: A Staff Report,", 1968-1969 (Box-folder 235: 6)
  - "Rights in Concord: A Staff Report,", 1969 (Box-folder 235: 7)
  - Riots and disorder at UC Berkeley, 1969 (Box-folder 235: 8)
  - Anti-war
    - Protests, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 235: 9-10)
    - Protests Assembly Bill 159, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 235: 11)
    - Demonstration, 1967 April 15 (Box-folder 236: 1-2)
    - Incidents, Oak, etc., 1967 (Box-folder 236: 3)
  - Campus draft opposition, 1968 (Box-folder 236: 4)
  - Davis, Angela, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 236: 5)
  - Military Department legislation, 1970 (Box-folder 236: 6)
  - Criminal law and procedure legislation, 1970 (Box-folder 236: 7-8)
  - Committee on Un-American Activities, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 236: 9)
  - Legislation, 1967-1974
    - Reference data on bills related to legal affairs section, 1968 (Box-folder 236: 10)
    - Legal affairs, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 236: 11-12)
    - Legal affairs (cont'd.), 1967-1974 (Box-folder 237: 1-3)
    - Possible legislation, legal affairs, 1968 (Box-folder 237: 4)
    - Legal affairs, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 237: 5-11)
    - Legal affairs (cont'd.), 1967-1974 (Box-folder 238: 1-2)
    - Political Reform Program, 1974 (Box-folder 238: 3)
    - Penal code changes, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 238: 4)
    - Bills analyzed for legislative section, 1968 (Box-folder 238: 5-6)
    - Prevention and control of riots and disorders, 1968 (Box-folder 238: 7)
    - AB 870, 1968 (Box-folder 238: 8)
    - Deadly weapons control, 1968 (Box-folder 238: 9)
    - Drugs and marijuana, 1968 (Box-folder 238: 10)
    - Eavesdropping, 1968 (Box-folder 238: 11)
    - Extradition and clemency, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 238: 12-13)
    - Governor's program, plans, etc., 1968 (Box-folder 238: 14)
    - SB 499 law enforcement, employee-management relations, 1968 (Box-folder 238: 15)
    - Marshalls, 1968 (Box-folder 238: 16)
    - Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box-folder 238: 17-18)
      Includes declassified records returned to file after March 2016 release by Hoover.
    - Peace officers status and authority, 1968 (Box-folder 238: 19)
    - Police review boards and ombudsman, 1968 (Box-folder 238: 20)
    - Pornography, 1968 (Box-folder 239: 1)
    - Property tax relief, 1968 (Box-folder 239: 2)
    - Staff conferences and meetings, 1968 (Box-folder 239: 3)
    - Tear gas, 1968 (Box-folder 239: 4)
    - AB 938, peace officer retirement, 1967 (Box-folder 239: 5)
    - SB 84, 1967 (Box-folder 239: 6-7)
    - AB 901,902, 1967 (Box-folder 239: 8)
    - Bills approved by governor, 1967 (Box-folder 239: 9)
    - Abortion, undated (Box-folder 239: 10)
    - Anti-riot, 1967 (Box-folder 239: 11)
    - Capital punishment, 1967 (Box-folder 239: 12)
    - CCP 1661b, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 239: 13)
    - Deadly weapons control, 1967 (Box-folder 239: 14)
    - Governor's crime program, 1967 (Box-folder 239: 15)
    - Juvenile court law, 1967 (Box-folder 239: 16)
    - Miscellaneous, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 239: 17-20)
    - Obscenity, 1967 (Box-folder 240: 1)
    - Police procedures, 1967 (Box-folder 240: 2)
    - Police review boards, ombudsman, etc., 1967 (Box-folder 240: 3)
    - Sealing of records, 1967 (Box-folder 240: 4)
    - State Bar Legislative Program, 1967 (Box-folder 240: 5)
    - State government, 1967 (Box-folder 240: 6)
    - Governor's anti-crime legislative program, 1967 (Box-folder 240: 7)
    - Reference material, 1966 (Box-folder 240: 8)
    - Criminal justice, corrections, 1969 (Box-folder 240: 9)
    - Task force on criminal justice legislation, 1969 (Box-folder 240: 10)
    - SB 1506 revised proposed criminal code, 1972 (Box-folder 240: 11)
  - Military
    - Emergency operations procedures, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 240: 12-16)
    - Emergency operations procedures (cont'd.), 1967-1971 (Box-folder 241: 1-7)
    - National Guard newspapers, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 241: 8)
    - Personnel, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 241: 9-11)
    - Aircraft, C-130/C-141, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 242: 1-2)
    - Defense contracts/military hardware, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 242: 3)
    - "Cable Splicer,", 1968 (Box-folder 242: 4)
    - "Cable Splicer II," after action report, 1969 (Box-folder 242: 5)
    - "Cable Splicer III,", 1969-1970 (Box-folder 242: 6-7)
    - California Specialized Training Institute (CSTI), 1971-1974 (Box-folder 242: 8-9)
    - California bases, 1968-1974 (Box-folder 243: 1)
    - California troop strength, 1967-1974 (Box-folder 243: 2-5)
    - Federal active duty, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 243: 6-9)
    - California National Guard, emergency status, Ed Meese order, original, 1970 (Box-folder 243: 10)
    - Military Department state active duty, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 243: 11)
    - Cost of emergency active duty, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 243: 12)
    - Use of National Guard as forest firefighters, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 243: 13)
    - Security of installations, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 243: 14)
    - Ronald Reagan/Edwin Meese/Herbert E. Ellingwood security clearance, 1974 (Box-folder 244: 1)
    - Retirement pay, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 244: 2)
    - Leave policy, 1969 (Box-folder 244: 3)
    - Budget, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 244: 4)
    - Department headquarters, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 244: 5)
    - General, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 244: 6-13)
    - "Sacramento Air Material Area (SMAMA) Management and Material Support Attributes" booklet, undated (Box-folder 245: 1)
    - California National Guard Domestic Action Program, 1971 (Box-folder 245: 2)
    - California military forces, emergency plan, 1967 (Box-folder 245: 3)
    - Maps, undated (Box-folder 246: 1-2)
    - Proposal to activate state military reserve, 1968 (Box-folder 246: 3)
    - Emergency readiness and operations manual, 1969 (Box-folder 246: 4-5)
    - Governor's Emergency Planning and Operations, School Conference, 1970 (Box-folder 246: 6-7)
    - Third Annual Emergency Planning and Operations, School Conference, 1971 (Box-folder 246: 8)
    - Reception for Lt. Governor Robert H. Finch, 1967 (Box-folder 246: 9)
    - Civil disorder management course, 1973 (Box-folder 246: 10)
    - Vital statistics, Mather Air Force Base, 1970 (Box-folder 247: 1)
    - Natural disaster activities, 1968 (Box-folder 247: 2)
    - Pictorial coverage of California floods, 1969 January (Box-folder 247: 3)
    - California Military Academy, 1970 (Box-folder 247: 4)
  - Office of Planning and Research
    - 1970-1974 (Box-folder 247: 5-7)
    - Federal planning grants, 1970 (Box-folder 247: 8)
    - 1968-1974 (Box-folder 247: 9-12)
    - 1968-1974 (cont'd.) (Box-folder 248: 1-3)
    - State development plan, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 248: 4-5)
    - Task Force on Reorganization of Council on Intergovernmental Relations and Local Planning Assistance Functions of State Planning Office, 1968 (Box-folder 248: 6)
    - California State Development Plan Program, 1968 (Box-folder 248: 7)
    - Report to the Lt. Governor on the state Office of Planning, 1970 (Box-folder 248: 8)
    - "State Planning in California: A Functional Analysis,", undated (Box-folder 248: 9)
  - Governor's Office, Advisory Coordinating Council on Public Personnel Management, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 248: 10-12)